casmiami.com 2019-03-24

# Privacy Policy

CASmiami.com recognizes that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami). If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at Privacy Matters, c/o College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami), 9050 NW 27th Ave, Miami, Florida 33147, USA.

 **Information we collect and how we use it.**

We offer a service that may require you to register for a login account and provide personal information to us. When you submit a request for a quote or request information on a specific vehicle, we may collect the following types of information:

Information you provide - When you submit a request, we will only ask you for personal information (such as your name, company name, telephone number, email address, self-assigned password, type of vehicle, odometer reading and a description of the vehicle in question).

User communications - When you provide email or other communication information to CASmiami.com, we may retain the communication information in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and correspond to improve our services.

Other sites - This Privacy Policy applies to only web sites and services that are owned and operated by CASmiami.com

College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami) only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising;
  * Sharing information to affiliates for the use of collecting or delivering a vehicle or vehicles in the process of completing a business transaction.
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services; 
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network;
  * and Developing new services.

 **Choices for personal information.**

When you submit a request for information or quotation, we may ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

 **Information sharing.**

College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami) will only share personal information with other affiliates, companies or individuals or any third party to complete a business transaction.If College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami) becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Please contact us at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

 **Information security.**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.We restrict access of personal information to College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami) employees, contractors and agents. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

Please note that information contained in emails are sent unencrypted from our offices, and therefore are **NOT SECURE**. In general, all email, mobile, and any electronic communications are not totally secure, and information can be lost, intercepted or modified. By instructing our company, you will have a personal relationship with us which should assist in avoiding some of the common scams carried out by fraudsters. If you do not wish us to communicate with you electronically (email, mobile, etc.,), you must advise us, otherwise we will assume your authority is given in this regard.

 **Cyber Security.**

CASmiami.com website utilizes secure socket layer **Hyper Text Transfer Protocol Secure** (HTTPS) & domain Certification to secure & assure the web visitor’s connection to the actual CASauto website. Since Cybercrime is becoming prevalent on a global level, and hackers are devising new technologies to defraud legitimate companies and their clients, visitors to our website must still exercise utmost caution. If you do not see the **HTTPS & lock icon** in the URL field and / or our ID Certification on our website has expired, we would advise you to leave the unsecured site. If you receive email purporting to be from us which is suspicious in sender and content, please phone us immediately before taking any action (i.e., sending funds by wire transfer, etc.,) and speak to the familiar sales representative you are dealing with to confirm such information conveyed in the email or its attachments. 

**Disclaimer.**

In General, Visitors & Clients should be diligent in securing their web browsing & Email activities throughout the internet by utilizing devices that have active antiviral / anti-malware software & firewalls. **Do NOT USE** unsecured devices and / or WIFI networks that are Open and Public since they are potential portals for cyber fraud.

College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami) will **Not Be Liable** for any vulnerabilities or financial loss that you may have incurred while browsing our website or any sites on the internet, including but not limited to your email & personal accounts. We will **NOT ACCEPT RESPONSIBILITY** if you transfer money into an incorrect account due to cyber fraud or by your error.

 **Enforcement.**

College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami) regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami)’s treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site or by writing to us at Privacy Matters, c/o College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami), 7900 NW 154th Street, Suite 200, Miami Lakes, FL 33016, USA.

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami)'s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between CASmiami.com and an individual.

 **Use of Cookies.**

A cookie is a small string of information that the website that you visit transfers to your computer for identification purposes. Cookies can be used to follow your activity on the website and that information helps us to understand your preferences and improve your website experience. Cookies are also used to remember for instance your user name and password. You can turn off all cookies, in case you prefer not to receive them. You can also have your computer warn you whenever cookies are being used. For both options you have to adjust your browser settings (like Internet Explorer). There are also software products available that can manage cookies for you. Please be aware though that when you have set your computer to reject cookies, it can limit the functionality of the website you visit and it's possible then that you do not have access to some of the features on the website. 

CASmiami.com uses or may use cookies in the following ways:

  * To store session information while users are browsing its websites.
  * To enable more accurate reporting of site usage data, such as new visitors, unique visitors and returning visitors.
  * To enable targeted content to be served on its sites or other third party sites based on your browsing history (see privacy considerations below). 

CASmiami.com may request and store personal information to customize your experience on our sites. We will never share this information with third parties without your consent, except where required by law.

 **Changes to this policy.**

Please note that this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site or at Privacy Matters, c/o College Auto Sales of Florida, LLC (CAS Miami), 9050 NW 27th Ave, Miami, FL, 33147 USA. Phone: (305)694-0000, E-Mail: [Webmaster@CASmiami.com](mailto:Webmaster@CASmiami.com)
